Chapter 1: One Act Before Trouble

Some time later, in the mountainous outskirts of the Galarc capital...

Orphia, the high elf girl, stood at a location with a fine view several kilometers from the capital of Galtuuk. There was no one else around her; she was moving separately from Miharu and the others in the royal castle in order to set up a destination point for teleportation sorcery.

The first step was to select a location. Barely anyone ever climbed this mountain, but she still had to use spirit arts to stabilize the terrain and secure the area. She put up a perception-blocking barrier and a field to conceal the disorder of magic essence after teleporting. There were a lot of steps, but she was finally done.

“Okay, the spell circle is stable and the barriers are complete... Now, Dissolvo.”

Just like how there were two stone houses, there were two Time-Space Caches. Orphia used hers to take out the teleport crystal she had borrowed from Rio in advance.

The destination registered in the crystal was the spirit folk village. Now that the preparations were complete, she had no need to remain here anymore. She would return to the village to bring Gouki and the others here to Galarc.

With Rio gone to retrieve Liselotte, she wouldn’t be able to bring them to the castle immediately, so they’d have to remain in the stone house until his return. But the original plan was to bring Gouki’s group over as soon as the preparations in Strahl were complete, so Gouki and the others were still waiting for that to happen.

“Instans Motus.” Orphia chanted a spell, activating the teleport crystal. The space around her immediately distorted—a sign of the sorcery activating. Just before she teleported, Orphia glanced over at the capital of Galtuuk. Then, just before the spell completed and moved her to the village, the sight of countless black shapes raining down on the capital caught her eyes.

“Wha...?”

The teleportation completed: what filled Orphia’s view now was the sight of the forest and spring near the spirit folk village. The scenery was extremely peaceful, but...

“What...was that...?”

Orphia’s face stiffened at the sinister omen she’d just witnessed.

“...”

She had a bad feeling about this. Propelled by her intuition, Orphia hurried towards the village.

◇ ◇ ◇

At roughly the same time, in the capital of the Beltrum Kingdom, Celia’s father, Count Roland Claire, was visiting the royal castle. He had been personally summoned by Duke Arbor himself.

“What matters did you wish to discuss today?” Roland asked after they had exchanged curt greetings with each other in a meeting room.

“Negotiations with the Restoration will be held in the near future. The location will be the Galarc Kingdom. I’d like you to attend, Count Claire,” Duke Arbor said, stating his demands simply.

“I see... But why me?” Roland feigned confusion as he sought more information.

After being suspected of assisting Christina out of the castle, he was essentially treated as a spy by Duke Arbor’s faction. There was no concrete evidence to convict him, but he had been relieved of his position in the capital and placed under the watch of a dispatch supervisor while managing the affairs of his territory. He had also been cut off from any news of the capital, so Roland wanted to use this chance to gain as much information as he could.

“You should have a lot of contacts with that side, no?” Duke Arbor said with blunt implication behind his words.

“Haha... I don’t think so.” Roland tried to brush off the question with a shrug.

“Your beloved daughter seems to have settled over there.” Duke Arbor pointed out how Celia, who was supposed to have been kidnapped from the wedding ceremony with Charles, was now a member of the Restoration.

Naturally, Duke Arbor was aware that Celia’s abduction had been arranged by Christina, who felt indebted to her from her academy days and wanted her to join the Restoration. Like the spies in Beltrum working for Duke Huguenot, there were spies in the Restoration working for Duke Arbor and keeping him informed.

“I was also bewildered by that news.” Roland sighed to express his lack of knowledge regarding Celia’s abduction.

Duke Arbor furrowed his brow at the sly reaction. “There’s no mistake that your daughter has settled over there. I have contacts who have seen her in person.”

“So it appears. I will not deny that it seems she has joined the Restoration,” Roland said, implying that he had objections to other accusations.

Duke Arbor looked at Roland with suspicion, but he knew it was futile to make accusations without any evidence—it had been as such since Christina first escaped Beltrum Castle.

He had no intention of digging further into either that or the connection between Roland and the Restoration. Duke Arbor chose to get on with the discussion. “Fine. In which case, it should be clear why your presence is requested.”

“However, I cannot imagine my presence making any difference. Are you saying you want me to attend just for numbers?”

Surely not, Roland implied in his tone as he tried to probe for more information from Duke Arbor.

“That’s right.” Duke Arbor nodded dismissively, preemptively cutting off any questions Roland could lead him towards.

He probably wanted to avoid giving Roland any unnecessary information, but his attitude could also be interpreted as that of a successful veteran soldier who loathed the bothersome tactics of civil officials. At any rate, probing any further against such an attitude would be like stirring the hornet’s nest for Roland.

“I see... I have no reason to refuse, then.”

Considering how unbalanced the relations were between Duke Arbor and Roland, there was no choice but to accept. He’d also be able to hear the state of affairs himself if he attended, so Roland obediently accepted without a fight.

“Then it’s decided. The negotiations will be held in the near future. I will send a messenger to your territory once the date is confirmed. I doubt I need to say this, but keep your schedule open.”

Duke Arbor stood up, indicating the end of their discussion. He made sure to add a snide remark about Roland’s lack of duties in the capital as well. Making Roland travel all the way out to the capital for a message like this was also a clear act of harassment, but Roland showed no particular irritation.

“Understood. I shall take my leave after finishing this cup of tea,” he said, picking up his teacup and sipping it gracefully.

“Hmph.” Duke Arbor snorted in disgust and left the room.

What Duke Arbor fears the most right now is nobles outside of his faction regaining power, but... Roland returned his teacup to its saucer and lost himself in his thoughts.

The Arbor family’s power had definitely lessened after Celia’s abduction from Charles’s wedding and Christina’s escape from the castle.

At the same time, there was a definite lack of anyone who could stand up to the Arbor faction in the present capital. Everyone had either been expelled from the capital and joined the Restoration, or been removed from their positions like Roland and lost power. So while there were signs of the Arbor faction’s decline, with no other force that could oppose them in the capital, their position was as strong as ever. The other nobles that pandered to Duke Arbor also received favorable treatment without Duke Huguenot’s faction around, so they had no reason to risk their positions by stirring things up.

Considering how he’s going to negotiate with the Restoration on equal terms—with me of all people present—he must be rather worried about his son being held hostage. Attending the negotiations is exactly what I wished for. I must use this chance to gain as much information as possible. I may even be able to see my little Celia.

Roland’s expression softened.

Celia... It seems she arrived in Rodania safely, but is she really happy over there? Her happiness...

But at the same time, he felt lonely. His expression became gloomy.

Well, I’m sure I can leave her in Princess Christina’s hands. And with that boy nearby, she should be well protected...

He recalled Rio, who had escorted Christina and Celia to Rodania. He had been worried half to death when Celia was abducted from the wedding, but those emotions had been replaced with true gratitude when he was told the truth of what had happened.

He understood that Celia trusted Rio. And that Celia had feelings for him.

Guh. There’s no doubt that she feels for him...

Now that he had caught on to his beloved daughter’s thoughts, he wanted nothing more than to support her happiness. This was the genuine truth, but a father’s parental love was complex.

What if in my absence, they... I won’t allow it. I definitely won’t allow it... They must marry first with me in attendance, at the very least... No, but there’d be no chance to hold a wedding in this situation... Even so, if he touches her before marriage... Or after marriage... Ah, but I do want to see my grandchildren’s faces. Hm. Hmm...

Roland lost himself to a spiral of negative thoughts. The only thing he could say for certain was—

I won’t forgive him if he makes Celia cry.

That much was simple.

What should I do if he makes her cry...? A demonstration of our family’s secret magic would be required at the very least...

Seriousness aside, Roland cared for Celia more than anyone else. Yet, at this moment, there was no way for him to know about the evil that was approaching his beloved daughter.

Chapter 2: Ambush

A short while before Orphia returned to the spirit folk village, some important guests were visiting Rio’s mansion on the Galarc Castle grounds.

“It’s been a while, Princess Christina, Princess Flora.”

They were Beltrum Kingdom’s First and Second Princess and the current Restoration leaders, Christina and Flora.

“Long time no see, Professor Celia.”

“It’s so nice to see you again!”

The two of them greeted Celia happily.

“You too. I’m so happy seeing you two again. It must have been a tiring trip here.”

“Not at all. Thank you for agreeing to see us on such short notice,” Christina said with a bow.

Second Princess Charlotte of the Galarc Kingdom was also there, but in Rio’s absence, Celia’s relationship with Christina and Flora made her best suited as host. Miharu and the other girls didn’t have any experience dealing with the noble class either, so she was the only option other than Charlotte.

Charlotte’s knight Louise and Christina’s knight Vanessa were waiting with the other guards outside the room.

“Unfortunately, Haruto is absent right now...”

“I would have liked to express my gratitude to Sir Amakawa, but the main purpose of my visit today concerns you, Professor Celia.”

Celia looked puzzled. “Me?”

“Yes. I’ve already informed Princess Charlotte—or rather, the Galarc Kingdom is already aware—but a meeting between the Restoration and the main Beltrum Kingdom will be held in the near future,” Christina said with a glance at Charlotte.

“That’s...”

“Starting with your wedding ceremony, Duke Arbor has had a string of failures to address. Charles and Alfred were taken prisoner, and I was able to escape and join the Restoration. I’m sure he’s quite panicked about it, as he has approached us for negotiations.”

“Has the ironclad Arbor family finally started losing its power?”

“It would appear so.”

At present, over a thousand of Beltrum Kingdom’s nobles had joined the Restoration, including spouses and children. But that was still a minority compared to the number of nobles the Arbor faction controlled in Beltrum. And in noble society politics, the size of the faction meant everything. That was why Duke Huguenot’s faction was unable to justify themselves and had lost their place in the capital.

However, power was an uncertain substance in noble society. This was because only a small fraction of the nobles in a faction were invested too deeply to back out—most nobles in the faction were able to switch sides to their convenience as circumstances changed.

In fact, many of the nobles in Duke Huguenot’s faction had joined Duke Arbor when his territory was lost to the Proxia Empire.

“We can’t let this opportunity slip through our hands, then.”

Duke Arbor’s failures could be used to regain those drifting nobles. Their distance from the capital made it difficult to physically contact those nobles, but Duke Arbor’s power was definitely weakening. If he was the one approaching for negotiations, they’d be able to turn things in their favor.

“We’re still in the midst of discussing our agenda for the negotiations, but they’ve requested the return of Charles and Alfred, as well as Alfred’s enchanted sword.”

Charles was Duke Arbor’s heir, and Alfred was the strongest knight in the country. The sword he used, the Light Blade of Judgment, was also a national treasure.

“They’re all powerful cards for negotiation.”

“Yes. And they were all given to us by Sir Amakawa. I wanted to thank him once again for his assistance, but... It seems like things are rather serious over here. I heard Sir Amakawa headed out to rescue Lady Liselotte.”

Christina was acquainted with Liselotte herself and sometimes kept in contact with her. Her expression clouded with worry.

“Sir Haruto will definitely bring Liselotte back to us,” Charlotte stated firmly, her posture upright and confident.

“Yes,” Celia agreed.

“That’s true. If it’s Sir Amakawa...” Christina nodded, biting back her words. She had witnessed his talents and strength up close and personal during the battle with Lucius in the Paladia Kingdom, which was why she believed in Rio as well.

“That’s right! Sir Haruto can definitely do it!” Flora said.

“I don’t know when he will return, but I will send a message out to you when he does,” Celia said cheerfully to Christina, hoping to wipe the gloomy expression from her face.

“Perhaps I can visit again when he returns with Lady Liselotte. We plan on staying in the Galarc Castle for a while.”

“Oh, really?”

“Yes. The meeting with the Beltrum Kingdom will almost certainly be held at the Galarc Castle, so the plan is to remain here until then.”

“In that case, we should hold a small party once Sir Haruto returns with Liselotte. I’ll be sure to invite the two of you,” Charlotte suggested after listening to their conversation.

“Oh, that would be lovely. Please do!” Flora immediately leapt at the chance, but—

“Flora.” Christina let out an exasperated warning as a reminder to restrain herself in the residence of a foreign noble.

“Oh, but only if it isn’t a bother to you...” Flora added with a blush, ashamed of her behavior.

“Neither a sleepover nor a dinner party will be any bother, so please don’t feel reserved,” Celia said with a giggle, looking at her fondly.

Charlotte agreed with a cheeky but charming grin. “Indeed. I have no right to speak as someone half living in this house out of everyone’s kindness, but please come over.”

She had succeeded in accompanying Satsuki to Rio’s mansion at every possible occasion until she had practically taken up residence there herself, but she also acted as King Francois’s messenger and the main point of contact for any nobles who wanted to get closer to Rio.

Whenever something was required, Charlotte would make the necessary arrangements at the speed of light. She did all her work, sometimes in unseen places, and had won over Rio’s trust enough for the residents of the mansion to accept her. There was even a room for her in the mansion.

“Thank you very much. Then, if you don’t mind...” Christina bowed, accepting the offer.

“Then it’s decided. Everyone will be delighted to have you there. They were wondering how the two of you have been doing,” Charlotte said to Christina and Flora.

“If there’s still time after this, we can invite them all over here,” Celia said.

Miharu and the others were inside the mansion, but had excused themselves from the meeting when they heard the visit was for official business with Celia. Only Orphia was elsewhere outside, but she would have come right away if invited as well.

“We wanted to greet everyone as well, so if you’re not too busy... We’re almost done with what we wanted from Professor Celia too.”

“Is there still something you needed from me?”

“Yes, as a continuation from earlier. If the circumstances suit you, would you be willing to attend the meeting with the Beltrum Kingdom?”

“Me...?” Celia blinked.

“In exchange for returning Charles, I am thinking of demanding several conditions that would benefit Count Claire and the rest of your family.”

“Could I ask the reason why...?” Celia asked hesitantly, shocked at the sudden proposal.

“It hasn’t been officially announced to the Beltrum Kingdom, but even they’ve noticed that you joined the Restoration after being abducted from your wedding ceremony. Count Claire was also suspected of having assisted my escape from the capital. As long as we have Charles, they wouldn’t dare to touch Count Claire, but...”

If the situation changed, the Claire family could be in danger.

“At any rate, there’s no doubt that the Claire family has taken the brunt of all these events. The upper ranks of the Restoration have agreed that it would be proper to compensate him.”

That’s why there was nothing to worry about, Christina implied.

Celia bowed her head in deep sincerity. “Thank you for considering my family.”

“Not at all,” Christina said, continuing the discussion. “We’re still reviewing what kind of conditions should be requested, but...”

It was at that moment.

Boom.

An explosion roared, shaking the room.

“What was that? Some kind of magic training?”

Celia immediately went to look out the window, followed by the others in the room. The booming sounds continued even as they moved. The source of the sound appeared to be scattered in various directions, some near and some far.

“No, it’s too loud to be coming from the training grounds of the castle. I believe the sound is either coming from the castle or somewhere nearby,” Charlotte guessed undauntedly, looking out the window.

After a short time, the sounds stopped.

“Excuse us for entering.”

Charlotte’s head guard Louise and the Beltrum sisters’ head guard Vanessa came into the room. They had both been waiting outside the door, so they naturally heard the noises as well. They both wore the same grim expressions.

“Can you tell what’s going on?” Charlotte asked Louise.

“No. I haven’t received any notice of an event that would create such noises either. The only option I can think of is magic training, but the sound came from too close by for that. I also saw something black fall from the sky through the window. I’ve sent my subordinates to check on the situation, and they’ll be back as soon as they know.”

“I see. In that case, shall we remain waiting in this mansion?”

“Yes. I’ve asked the guards who accompanied us to the mansion to station themselves outside. But please relocate to the safe room just in case.”

The safe room was a place for important figures to evacuate to in times of emergency. The level of refuge varied depending on the type of emergency likely to occur, but they were all made to be secure from outside attack.

This mansion was located on castle grounds, so the castle served as the evacuation point in true times of emergency. Thus, the safe room here was only a simple one.

“All right. Let’s group up with Lady Satsuki and the others first,” Charlotte immediately decided.

“We’re coming in, Char.”

Just then, with Satsuki in the lead, she, Miharu, Latifa, Sara, and Alma entered the room where they were holding their meeting. They must have heard the unnatural explosions and felt the abnormal air, as they all had worried looks on their faces. Sara and Alma even held their weapons just in case.

“You heard that loud noise earlier?” Satsuki asked.

“Yup. We don’t normally hear something like that around here, so we were shocked...” Miharu replied.

“We’re not sure of the situation either, but we were going to go to the safe room just in case. The knights have gone to check things out. Will you come with us?”

“I see... And yes, please.”

Satsuki exchanged a look with Miharu and nodded. At this point, there was still no clear danger, so there was no real sense of urgency yet, but...

“R-Reporting! A group of monsterlike creatures has descended upon the castle!”

“Wha...”

One of Charlotte’s knights came running in a panic, heightening the tension.

“Calm down. What do you mean by monsterlike creatures? Are they not goblins or orcs?” Louise asked her subordinate calmly. Powerful monsters like minotaurs had been commonplace in the Divine War that took place a thousand years ago, but goblins and orcs were the only monsters left in the modern era. There were some exceptions to that rule, but not even adventurers that worked in monster subjugation encountered them very often. Most of them reached retirement without ever seeing a different kind of monster.

“I only saw the knights fighting from afar, but their movements were much faster than those of a goblin or orc. I’ve never seen such a monster before. Their shapes were rather humanoid, but the ferocious expressions on their faces were monstrous. Some had gray skin while others had black skin,” the knight reported.

“Huh...?” Miharu looked shocked, and Satsuki noticed.

“I see. Any information about their numbers and locations?”

“I’m sorry, I prioritized my return to the mansion... However, they appear to have fallen across the grounds. There are battles taking place everywhere.”

Louise didn’t seem to have noticed the change in Miharu, so Satsuki waited for the subordinate to finish speaking. “What’s wrong, Miharu?” she asked, bringing everyone’s attention to her.

“Oh, umm. When I first came to this world, some strange monsters appeared on the outskirts of Amande. Haruto and Ai-chan exterminated them, but they weren’t goblins or orcs. Maybe they’re the same monsters that appeared here?”

“I remember seeing the same monsters during the attack on Amande. They weren’t as strong as minotaurs, but they were fast and powerful,” Celia recalled with a frown. “It would take at least a knight with enhanced physical abilities to take them on...”

“I was there too.” Flora proceeded to give her account of what she had witnessed when she was kidnapped by Lucius in Amande.

“I see... We can’t say for sure, but it’s very likely that they’re the same monsters. The knights have thankfully intercepted them, but any monsters they miss could slip through to this mansion. We will secure the surroundings, so please head to the safe room immediately, Your Highness,” Louise urged.

“I understand,” Charlotte said. She then turned to the group. “Princess Christina, Princess Flora, please come with me. Lady Satsuki and everyone else too.”

“We will assist the guards outside,” Sara offered. At present, she and Alma were the strongest in the mansion, but...

“Oh... That’s...” Louise hesitated. She sparred with Sara and Alma on a daily basis so she knew their strength firsthand, but the two of them were still subjects of her guard.

“Alma and I have the role of protecting Miharu and the others in Haruto’s absence. There is no need to include us as subjects of protection. It’d be easier for us to move around outside than to have no information locked inside.”

“Well, that’s how it is. You don’t need to worry about Sara and me.”

Sara and Alma were both calm, as though they were familiar with such situations.

“...”

Satsuki looked like she was about to say something, but swallowed her words. I will protect this mansion as well—those were the words on the tip of her tongue, but she became uneasy. She understood her position as hero and feared her lack of combat experience would make her a hindrance.

Charlotte noticed Satsuki moving her mouth and purposefully gave Louise a push without looking at Satsuki. “Then we shall rely on you. There aren’t enough people in this mansion right now, and you two are probably the strongest with your enchanted swords.”

“Understood. We shall rely on you.” Louise bowed her head at Sara and Alma.

Sara turned around. “Latifa, you stay with Satsuki and Miharu. We’re counting on you to protect them if the need arises.”

“Okay! Leave it to me!” Latifa nodded firmly in agreement.

“Umm, I’m going to go with the two of them,” Celia stated.

“Huh?”

Everyone looked at her in surprise.

“Monsters drop enchanted gems and disappear when defeated, and you need someone on that side to confirm they’re the same monsters that appeared in Amande last time. I can cast healing magic if needed, and it would be useful to have a sorcerer in the back line. I’ve also trained with Sara and Alma in team fighting before,” Celia said, explaining herself to convince Christina and Charlotte more than Sara and Alma.

“While we would be most grateful to have a sorcerer of your caliber on the back line... There’s no need to expose yourself to danger like that.” Charlotte gave Celia a searching look as though to confirm the truth of her thoughts. Nobles who didn’t pursue military careers still went through some form of combat training, so she knew that Celia had basic fighting skills.

Because of that, it wasn’t unusual for them to join the battlefield when needed—in fact, it was seen as one of the duties of the noble class. However, it depended on the time and place. In the current situation, there was only a slight chance of a monster being missed by the knights. It’d be preferable to keep a count’s daughter protected rather than to have her fight.

“I’d like to do what I can in Haruto’s absence,” Celia replied calmly and clearly. Her intentions were evident on her face—that she wanted to fight, that she didn’t always have to be protected, that Haruto could rely on her if he needed to.

“We’re familiar with Celia’s magic skills, and it would be most reassuring to have her support,” Sara added in approval.

“I see... In that case, it would be insensitive of me to stop you,” Charlotte accepted in a slightly envious tone, glancing at Christina. Although Celia was currently Rio’s assistant, she was still a noble of the Restoration. Christina’s opinion also mattered.

“I will leave it to your discretion, Professor,” Christina said, nodding.

“Thank you very much. Let’s do this, Sara, Alma.”

“Right.”

Sara and Alma were both warriors. Since they’d started living with Celia, they understood her intentions well—and so they nodded firmly.

Beside them, Louise was discussing how to proceed with Vanessa.

“Please go with the princesses and guard the safe room.”

“Understood.”

“In that case, everyone should head through this door that’s connected to the safe room. I will station several knights in this drawing room just in case.”

With the necessary arrangements done, Louise pointed to a different door from the exit. There were three safe rooms in the mansion, and one of them was located in the drawing room for the sake of important guests.

Thus, the residents of the mansion split into those taking refuge in the safe room and those going outside to stand guard.

◇ ◇ ◇

Around the same time, a man floated in the skies above the capital, looking down at the castle grounds below him. It was the perpetrator behind the release of monsters across the grounds—Reiss himself. Less than an hour ago, he had been observing the fierce battle between Rio and Saint Erica from afar, but he had used a disposable teleport crystal to move to the Galarc Castle in an instant.

At present, the noncombatants of the castle were panicking while the knights fought the revenants throughout the castle grounds.

The first movement after sending out my precious magic-sealing orbs and revenants. Hopefully it’ll be enough to smoke someone out... Oh?

Reiss narrowed his eyes. His gaze fixed onto a single point from far above. It was the mansion Rio was gifted by Francois, and Celia, Sara, and Alma had just left through the front door.

It would’ve been problematic if they had shut themselves away inside the castle, so this is perfect. But it’s best not to underestimate those girls when they’re outside. I’ll hold nothing back.

A jet-black shadow sprung from Reiss’s feet, spreading across the blue sky. Five black orbs several meters in diameter appeared.

All five orbs rained down on Rio’s mansion like meteorites. Each descent was accompanied by a booming roar, shaking the building.

That’s all the revenants I have on hand. But I fear they won’t last long against those girls—better call those guys over as quickly as possible.

Once he had watched the orbs land, Reiss took out a new teleport crystal and smirked, rising even higher into the sky.

◇ ◇ ◇

After exiting the mansion, Sara walked along the outer wall of the building and moved on top of the roof for a better view. She strained her eyes to look over the area, checking that there were no monsters near the mansion.

“There are no monsters approaching the mansion as of yet. Though there are some people fighting here and there...”

She descended to the ground and reported what she saw to Louise and her knights, Celia, and Alma.

“Thank you. Though I would like to send assistance to our allies, we cannot leave our stations. Let us prioritize the protection of this mansion.”

As long as there was a chance of monsters reaching the mansion, they couldn’t afford to leave the mansion guards shorthanded. It was a shame they could only watch their allies fight from afar, but it was the right tactical decision to make. They considered the option of bringing Miharu and the others to the castle, but it wouldn’t be wise to risk the safety of so many noncombatants while on the move.

“I will continue keeping watch from the roof.”

“I will assist.”

With that, Sara and Alma left to climb the roof. It was at that moment that the black orbs Reiss had released fell down nearby. Thundering shock waves surged upon them, blowing up a cloud of dirt.

“Wha...?!”

Their vision was suddenly stolen, leaving them speechless. Meanwhile, the dark surfaces of the orbs that had fallen started melting away. There were a total of five orbs, and they were less than a hundred meters away from the mansion. Twelve revenants leaped out of each orb.

“Kshaaah!”

Sixty revenants started running at Sara and the others before the mansion. There were only a few that could defend against such a surprise attack.

“A-Alma and I will stand at the front!”

“Everyone else, focus on protecting Celia and preventing any strays from getting into the mansion!”

The first to respond were Sara and Alma.

“Duo Magi: Maius Terra Murum!!!” Meanwhile, Celia cast a spell while touching the ground with both hands. Less than two seconds later, two walls of earth appeared between them and the revenants. The walls were each one meter thick, five meters wide, and ten meters tall. The purpose of setting up the obstacles wasn’t to stop the revenants’ approach, but to avoid a situation where they were overwhelmed by the enemy’s advantage in numbers. The walls Celia created had a one-meter gap in between. This reduced the revenants’ options to passing through the gap, going the long way around, or climbing over the tops of the walls.

Restricting the enemy’s invasion route meant they could focus their firepower to where it was needed most. Being able to reduce the number of enemies to face at once was a huge benefit as well.

“Sara, Alma!” Celia yelled. “Please assume a formation surrounding me! Alma, you take the right side!”

“Got it!”

Sara and Alma understood Celia’s intentions instantly and split up to the left and right. The revenants had chosen not to climb the walls, but to advance through the middle and around the sides. As a result...

“Tres Magi: Ignis Iecit!”

“Haaah!”

“Hmph!”

The revenants coming from the middle, left, and right were met with powerful attacks from Celia, Sara, and Alma respectively.

“Grah!”

Three magic circles for sorcery spells appeared before Celia. One of them released a one-meter-wide fireball that blew back several of the revenants coming from the middle. The other two magic circles remained on standby beside her.

A lance of ice shot out of Sara’s dagger and pierced through several bodies at once, while Alma’s mace mowed down multiple enemies with a swing.

“They’re the same monsters I saw in Amande! Their skin is hard and they’re very tenacious, so be careful! The black ones move faster than the gray ones!” Celia shouted, warning Sara and the others about their characteristics. As though to prove her words, the enemies at the front staggered back to their feet even though their skin was now half-melted.

Out of the enemies Alma attacked, only the one at the very front died; the others behind it were already getting back up on their feet. The revenants pierced through the abdomen by Sara’s ice lance weren’t killed by just that attack either, and were squirming to pull the lance out.

“So it seems...!”

Sara summoned a long blade of ice to enshroud her dagger, beheading the revenants that were impaled on the ice lance. They finally died after that, the bodies vanishing and leaving behind enchanted gems.

“How troublesome!” Alma brushed aside an enemy that threw itself at her and swung her mace at the new revenants charging. It seemed that a clear hit from her mace was enough to kill them, as the one sent flying soon vanished.

Celia also fired the second and third fireball shots she had on standby from her multicasting, finishing off the revenants she missed the first time.

“...” Louise and the other knights were speechless at how unfazed Celia and the others were at the sudden ambush. They understood one another’s fighting styles and trained with each other every day, so there was nothing more reassuring. It was truly splendid.

In particular, Celia’s first move with the earth wall was a fine tactic against the revenants. Her ability to cast multiple intermediate spells at a rapid speed and calmly observe the enemy’s movements at the spur of the moment was incredibly impressive.

Louise looked at Celia in awe. “Defend Lady Celia so that her magic isn’t obstructed! Don’t overlook any monsters that run for the mansion!”

She pulled herself together and gave her subordinates orders. Only six or seven enemies had been defeated so far—the revenants were still advancing upon them.

“Sextus Magi: Ictus Lancea!” Celia seemed to get an idea from watching Sara’s ice lances and used her magic to create thirty-six spears of ice at once. She saw how piercing once wasn’t enough to kill and prepared multiple to make up for it.

The role of a sorcerer during group battles was to focus their firepower on the approaching enemies and reduce their numbers. Celia was trying to fulfill that role, but casting thirty-six spells simultaneously was a challenge even for a royal sorcerer. Although it was basic magic, the fact Celia had accomplished such a feat in the midst of battle left the knights around her shocked.

Ignoring the knights’ reaction, Celia continuously fired ice spears from the magic circle above her head. She stopped the revenants from approaching through the gap between the walls one after another.

Calm down and observe carefully... A sorcerer on the back line needs to have a broad view of the enemy’s movements and the ability to make preemptive moves.

Celia took a deep breath and focused on staying calm. Of course, she was nervous about fighting for real—in fact, she was terrified.

However, Celia knew firsthand what it was like to be a burden on the battlefield. The frustration of being immobilized by fear. She recalled the events leading up to her arrival at the Restoration.

“Tch. The blood loss will be an annoyance, but at least I didn’t get the heart.” Lucci chose to leave Alma lying there, not bothering to stop her bleeding. Instead, he turned his attention to Celia.

“A-Alma!” Celia shrieked from within the magic barrier.

“Gwaaark!” With its contract master defeated, Ifritah roared furiously. It abandoned the other mercenaries to lunge at Lucci.

“Damn it, leave the monster to me! Bring that barrier down right now!” Now, Lucci had no choice but to face Ifritah.

“Guh...” Alma took that chance to secretly cast healing spirit arts to stop her bleeding.

◇ ◇ ◇

Meanwhile, inside the mansion, shortly before Alma was stabbed by Lucci...

During times of war, the group holding the castle had to pay particular care to secure their field of view. Holding the castle meant they were protected by the building itself and could hide themselves, but at the same time, it meant their view of any incoming enemies was obstructed.

Defenselessly exposing oneself to incoming enemies by monitoring the outside was a problem, but hiding away out of fear of being discovered wasn’t good either. At worst, it was possible for the approaching enemy to invade without notice.

However, short of constructing forts intended for battle, it was difficult to design buildings with securing a field of view or preventing invasion in mind. Rio’s mansion was constructed with a focus on aesthetics, so it wasn’t suitable for holding during a siege.

Presently, right beside the drawing room where Satsuki and the others were hiding, Ven and his group of mercenaries were sneaking closer. They communicated to each other with hand signs while checking inside each window for their targets.

Then, they hit their jackpot: they could see Miharu and Satsuki inside the room. Farther inside the room was a passage that led to a safe room.

It’s here.

One of the mercenaries signaled with a hand sign. There were a total of four men outside the window, including Ven. They decided on their roles and silently began their invasion.

“Magicae Murum.”

One of the men activated a spell to set a magic barrier in front of them and started charging towards the window.

“Haaah!” Latifa, who had been hiding in the corner of the ceiling above the window, fired a ball of magic essence at the unguarded mercenary’s head.

“Wha?!” Taking an attack to the head was enough for even a physically enhanced body to fall unconscious. The first mercenary who entered collapsed to the floor. However, they had accounted for the possibility of an ambush. Seeing one of their men go down wasn’t enough to shake the others outside, and they responded rapidly.

“Above the window!”

“Photon Projectilis!”

One of the mercenaries aimed above the window, hoping to eliminate Latifa from the other side of the wall.

“Aah!” Latifa backed away from the window immediately. She spun midair and landed on the floor.

“The enemy’s here! Miharu, go back into the room!”

“R-Right!”

At Satsuki’s order, Miharu promptly headed for the safe room.

Satsuki’s side was naturally aware of the possibility of an outside attack. They could have all hidden in the safe room to remove the risk of being spotted from the window, but there was no way of hiding the passage to the safe room itself. Considering the likelihood of the enemy coming inside to check, they decided to set a trap. Miharu had been placed in the drawing room on purpose, to act as though they were defenseless.

“Next!”

“Magicae Murum!”

Another mercenary cast a magic barrier, attempting to enter again.

“I won’t let you!”

However, Satsuki was waiting with her Divine Arms. She fired a wind bullet of materialized magic essence from the end of her spear, hitting the barrier of the mercenary at the front.

“Whoa!” The mercenary who received the attack was sent flying several meters back out of the mansion.

“Get inside!” Ven and the remaining mercenary entered the room.

“Haaah!” The first to move was Latifa. With daggers in both hands, she leaped at one of the invading men.

“Tsk. Whoa, there...”

The mercenary immediately lifted his sword to take Latifa’s attack. She followed up with several swings of her daggers, but they were all parried away.

“...”

Latifa retreated with a light step, putting one meter of distance between herself and the man. Her expression was stiff, and her hands clutching the daggers were trembling.

“She’s fast, but...” The mercenary instantly perceived that she either had little experience when it came to killing another person, or felt some kind of aversion to it.

“Don’t let your guards down. She’s stronger than the knights outside,” Ven warned his men as he faced Satsuki.

“I know. But who’s the target?” The man facing Latifa no longer looked like he was underestimating her.

“Any of the ones at the back will do. These ones will just get in the way, so eliminate them.”

“Roger that.”

Having exchanged the necessary information, Ven and his men prepared for battle.

“Barging into someone’s home like this...” Satsuki muttered, her body trembling.

Ven furrowed his brow. “Huh?”

“...means you’re willing to be treated as intruders, right? This is justified self-defense!”

“Huh? What are you... Whoa!”

Satsuki suddenly accelerated, closing in on Ven. She then swung her spear with all her might. Ven reflexively went to block the spear with his sword.

“Haaah!” Satsuki swung her spear through, knocking Ven away bodily. In response to her anger, her Divine Arms boosted her physical body far more than an imitation enchanted sword.

“Ngh...” Ven was blown backwards with great force. He crashed into the window and toppled outside of the mansion.

“Are you serious...? Hey, Ven, you okay?!” the remaining mercenary in the room yelled.

“Y-Yeah!” Ven staggered to his feet and yelled back. He had received some damage, but he was fortunate enough to block most of the attack itself with his sword. As he was rolling backwards, he was able to adjust his landing to fall safely.

“Get out of here already!”

Satsuki charged at the remaining mercenary in the room.

“Tch.”

The man seemed to realize there was no good in remaining in the room. He retreated through the window.

“I won’t let you get away!” Satsuki chased him out the window.

“W-Wow, Satsuki...”

Latifa was taken aback by the sudden turn of events. But she soon snapped to her senses and rushed over to the window to check on the situation.

Ifritah’s out in the open! A-Alma!

She must have realized Ifritah was going wild from the sound of its roars. Latifa watched on as Ifritah lunged at Lucci, while Louise ran with Alma in her arms.

◇ ◇ ◇

Meanwhile, far above in the skies where no griffin could reach, Reiss manipulated bullets of light to provide support to Arein and the others on the ground as he observed the battle. Although he could control their trajectories, he was quite a distance away from his targets. His accuracy was low, but it was enough to keep the kingdom’s aerial knights back.

I knew there was a bird mid-class spirit here, but I hadn’t expected any others... They must be demi-humans of the Wilderness after all, Reiss thought, guessing Alma’s identity. He had previously seen a bird mid-class spirit patrolling the area when Rio was escorting Christina to Rodania.

Giving that sword to Lucci was the right decision. That sword is great against spirits. It should be able to take on a mid-class one easily. Though he seems to be struggling... And I don’t see the other two outside either.

The “other two” that Reiss was thinking of were Sara and Orphia. If Alma was contracted to a mid-class spirit, it made sense that one of the other two was contracted to the bird spirit.

If two of them are contracted to mid-class spirits, then the third is likely to have one as well... I could deal with the bird one if it appeared in the sky, but another mid-class spirit on the ground would be troublesome.

With one of them materialized with no regard for the human witnesses, it wouldn’t be strange for the other two to appear at any moment. Reiss hummed in thought as he focused on the movements taking place near the mansion.

The Heavenly Lions were all experienced fighters. They didn’t have any secret abilities, but they were all equipped with imitation enchanted swords that could enhance their physical bodies, an effect stronger than magic. They had enough strength to take on a mid-class spirit as a group. Most importantly, they were here to avenge Lucius, making their movements sharper than ever.

However, although the two most dangerous people—Rio and Aishia—weren’t here, the people around Rio were formidable as well. A hidden weapon had just appeared outside the mansion in the form of a mid-class spirit, and Ven’s group had gone through a window just moments ago, but was promptly chased back out. The situation everywhere was changing by the moment.

There’s a spirit’s presence outside the capital? This is...the second mid-class spirit? But why is it outside?

Reiss redirected his attention from Rio’s mansion below to the edge of the royal capital. Then, he cast his gaze over to the mountainous region a few kilometers away from the capital, where he saw a huge bird several meters in size flying.

Things involving this boy never go according to plan... I’ll have no choice but to use my trump card. That, and a number of the revenants remaining on the ground...

Reiss returned his gaze to Arein and the others below, ceasing his support fire to hold his hand at the ground instead. But nothing visible happened. After a few seconds of maintaining that pose, Reiss began to fly towards the outskirts of the capital.

Moments later, the remaining revenants on the ground all started charging for Rio’s mansion at once.

“Umm, don’t ask me... But, I agree. You thought it’d be easier to take on everyone in the castle than Haruto. A rather arrogant view to have.” Satsuki smiled more like her usual self.

“Indeed. So, let’s show them. Abduct us if you can,” Charlotte said, provoking the assailants.

“Ha! Doesn’t that sound interesting, Ven?” Lucci walked up to them, ready to face Satsuki.

“I told you to go back to your post, damn it.”

“I’m outside the mansion, aren’t I? Plus, a bunch of easy targets just came outside to offer themselves. They seem to enjoy talking big, so I should naturally teach them their places, no? The tiny sorcerer can be dealt with by the people I left behind.”

Alma had collapsed and Ifritah was gone, so there was no one left to protect Celia’s barrier. The only ones left standing were Celia and seven knights that could only enchant their physical abilities with magic.

Three mercenaries with physical body enchantments could easily overwhelm them in no time. Like Lucci had said, there were enough people remaining for that. Meanwhile...

“What should we do? We put on a brave front, but the only ones who can move around and fight are Latifa, Vanessa, and myself. If they push past us, we can’t protect you all... We even brought Princess Christina and Princess Flora out here... Is that okay?” Satsuki whispered quietly to Charlotte.

“Flora and I are greatly indebted to Sir Amakawa, and these men were involved in our abduction as well. It is our duty as royalty to stand and fight in times of need. Let us offer what little power we have to the cause.”

“Yes! I’ll do my best for Sir Haruto!”

“Please don’t worry about us,” Christina said resolutely. Flora also seemed worked up—possibly because the matter involved Rio—as she was unusually enthusiastic.

“Don’t worry. It seems like Lady Miharu and Lady Latifa have a plan,” Charlotte said, glancing at Miharu beside her.

“Latifa...and Miharu?”

Satsuki looked at Miharu worriedly. They had been friends for a long time, and she knew Miharu didn’t have the personality type for conflict. She couldn’t imagine her fighting.

“Yes, please leave it to me.” Miharu looked a little nervous, but she nodded with strong determination.

“At my signal, Miharu will take her place and the battle will begin,” Latifa explained. “Satsuki and I will be the vanguards, and the princesses will support us with magic. If the enemy comes near, create a barrier with magic. Understood?”

“Yup, got it,” Satsuki said. She was still a little concerned for Miharu.

“Yes, leave it to us. I’m starting to get excited.” Although it had to be her first time experiencing such a thing, Charlotte looked like she was enjoying the situation.

“I have no objections either.”

“Yes!” Christina and Flora also replied.

“Then here goes...!” Latifa took a deep breath. “Now, Hel!” she yelled.

“Grrrah!” Sara’s contract spirit, a silver wolf, appeared, with Miharu riding its back.

“Wha?!”

“There’s another one of those monsters?!”

For a brief moment, Lucci and Ven froze.

“Go, Hel!” Miharu clung tightly to Hel’s back as it charged forward faster than the eye could follow. It weaved its way through the mercenaries until it arrived before the magic barrier Celia had cast.

“Miharu!”

“Celia!”

“H-Help Lady Miharu inside!”

Miharu jumped off of Hel’s back and rushed over the dirt wall with the help of the knights. The group over here had originally been planning to take down parts of the barrier for the knights to rush out, but the start of Latifa’s strategy had put an end to that idea. With Hel fighting in place of the knights, the situation turned in their favor.

“Wh-What’s happening?” Celia asked, bewildered.

“I’m going to help Ifritah materialize once more.”

“Y-You can do that?!”

Miharu nodded assuringly. “Yes. As long as I supply the magic essence needed.”

Spirits weren’t able to be physically harmed in their spirit forms, but their material forms could be damaged. Their physical abilities would decline if they maintained a wounded material form, and their bodies would disperse entirely if they sustained too much damage, but it wouldn’t result in their death. They were simply forced back into their spirit form. If the necessary essence was resupplied, they could regain their material form without issue.

The problem, however, was regaining that essence. Whether it was magic or spirit arts, the more unnatural the phenomenon occurring was, the greater the amount of magic essence needed. And it was highly unnatural for a spiritual existence to take a material form. That’s why it took a considerable amount of essence for a spirit to materialize. And it would take even more for a wounded spirit to regain an unwounded body.

Because of this, uncontracted spirits would take time naturally storing essence themselves, but a contracted spirit could receive essence from their contract partner and recover in an instant. Furthermore, humanoid spirits like Aishia could freely absorb essence from their contract partner through their connected path.

But that wasn’t the case for mid-class spirits like Ifritah. Whenever it needed essence, the contract partner had to be the one to supply it. However, Alma was currently unconscious and unable to prepare any magic essence.

“I’m going to send you magic essence, Ifritah. You’re listening, right? Here goes...”

Miharu would form a temporary contract with Ifritah in order to send it the essence it needed. The spirit needed to be the one to accept a temporary contract, but Miharu was well trusted by Alma, so that wouldn’t be a problem.

In terms of pure combat power, Miharu was indeed the weakest amongst the residents of the stone house. However, when it came to magic essence, Miharu had more than everyone but Rio. No matter how many times Hel and Ifritah were wounded, she would be able to bring them back without issue.

The main concern was the distance required for a temporary contract partner to supply magic essence—they had to be right beside each other. However...

“Grr!”

Ifritah made a full recovery outside the magic barrier. Hel and Ifritah—with these two mid-class spirits on the battlefield, the battle at Galarc Castle was about to reach its climax.

◇ ◇ ◇

On one side of the battle were Lucci, who was equipped with the jet-black sword formerly used by Lucius, and thirteen mercenaries including Ven, who were equipped with enchanted sword imitations that, while not as powerful as their genuine counterparts, could still provide physical enhancements superior to ability-boosting magic.

Facing them were Satsuki with her Divine Arms and Latifa with her physical body enhanced by spirit arts. Alma was still unconscious inside Celia’s magic barrier.

“Ha ha, how wonderful. As expected of Lady Orphia.” Gouki chuckled heartily at the sight of Orphia’s grand method of eliminating the monsters. He then turned back to Lucci, the last remaining enemy. “Now, shall we put an end to this?”

“Eat shit!” Lucci yelled, making a dash towards Gouki. Gouki also launched himself forward. The two were soon within reach of each other and swinging their weapons.

Swords crossed faster than the eye could see, during which Gouki started a conversation. “Hmph! I just don’t understand!” he shouted.

“Understand what?!” Lucci yelled back

“Why are you so mad? What reason do you have to be so emotional?”

“One of my comrades was killed!”

“While it sounds like you have perfectly reasonable values, your actions are completely contradictory! How can you value your own comrades while stealing the lives of others?”

“It’s survival of the fittest! Anyone who isn’t a comrade is of no concern to me! There’s no contradiction anywhere!”

“That isn’t much of an answer!”

It was at this point that Gouki’s katana sent Lucci flying with his sword. Lucci’s body had a more powerful physical enhancement thanks to Lucius’s enchanted sword, but Gouki’s body was enhanced with spirit arts. They were equally powerful enchantments, but their base strength was different.

“Shit!” Lucci backed away furiously. There was no leisure in his expression at all. He was unable to keep up with Gouki’s attacks, and shallow cuts began to accumulate over his body.

“Let me change the question, then. If you believe in both survival of the fittest and valuing your comrades, why do you direct your resentment to Sir Haruto, who’s stronger than all of you? Explain that contradiction. Sir Haruto is the one who defeated your leader. Survival of the fittest means you either surrender or hide yourselves once your leader is dead.”

Gouki temporarily put some distance between them and pointed the end of his sword at Lucci to ask his question. Why challenge Haruto if that was the case?

“What... Ngh!” Lucci was about to let his emotions snap, but found himself stumbling over his words instead. He was unable to come up with a logical reason.

“Hmph, no answer again. You’re a child with no sense of reason.”

“I’d rather die than answer such a pathetic question!” Lucci yelled. His pride wouldn’t allow such a thing.

“Then die! If there’s someone you refuse to surrender to while believing in survival of the fittest, your only options as a warrior are to die challenging them or to quietly kill yourself somewhere out of sight,” Gouki rebuked him sharply. That was what it meant to truly believe in the concept of “survival of the fittest.”

“Ngh...!”

“You can’t even do that, so you harass him behind his back. How laughable! You only claim survival of the fittest when it’s convenient to you. Those are the actions of nothing more than a vain coward!”

“Sh-Shut up! We came to take hostages so he wouldn’t run away! That’s how mercenaries work!” Lucci howled like a cornered dog.

“Hmm... The same mercenary that’s seeking revenge for his leader and comrades? I thought mercenaries were all about fighting for money. How pitiful.”

You don’t even know your own reason for being here right now, Gouki implied with a look that bordered on mercy instead of contempt.

“Grr...”

“But I can understand you a little more now. There’s no justice in your revenge—you have no reason at all. You just want to resent someone. If you value your comrades, you shouldn’t have laid your hands on other people’s comrades. I hope you can understand this one day...” Gouki trailed off, readjusting his katana’s position. Perhaps he had started this conversation in order to vent his feelings for the man who killed Ayame and Zen. Or perhaps he wouldn’t feel content without getting the last word in against the fiends who tried to harm his master.

“And regret it deeply for the rest of your life!” Gouki started running, closing the distance between them once more.

“Gah! Ugh— Argh, shit!”

The difference in their physical abilities was minimal, yet Lucci couldn’t keep up with Gouki’s sword movements. The more Gouki swung his sword, the slower Lucci’s reaction speed was.

Sh-Shit, I barely have any essence left as is.

It was all he could do to maintain his physical body enhancement. At this rate, he would lose.

On top of losing the logical argument, he was about to lose in sword mastery. With nothing but complete defeat on the horizon, Lucci began to panic.

“Hmph. Your agitation is showing in your sword. You’re full of openings!” Gouki saw through that panic and used that delayed reaction to slide right up to Lucci. He then swung his katana up from left to right.

“Wha—?!” Lucci tried to respond by defending, but his black sword sailed through the air.

“Fuck...” The hand that held the sword was also knocked upwards, causing the upper half of Lucci’s body to bend back.

“Justice!” Gouki flipped his blade at the end of the first swing and stepped forward, striking Lucci with the back of the sword before sliding past his side.

“Gah...” Lucci groaned, collapsing to the ground.

“It’s over.” With his back to the fallen man, Gouki moved with elegance, sheathing his katana with a clink.

“Gouki!” Latifa called Gouki’s name happily, waving her hand.

“Good day, Lady Latifa.” Gouki’s expression, having been sharp throughout the entire battle, immediately softened as he walked over to her.

“Thank you for saving us!”

“It is my duty to protect everyone. Lady Orphia told us of the ominous shapes she saw falling over the castle, so we rushed over here. It was lucky we did so.”

“Lady Latifa, may I ask who this is? He seemed to refer to Sir Haruto as his master during the battle, but...”

Charlotte had just finished ordering the knights to restrain the intruders and carry the wounded to the mansion. She questioned Latifa about the curious information her sharp ears had picked up on during the battle.

“My name is Gouki Saga. I served Sir Haruto’s late mother while she was alive.” Gouki introduced himself respectfully in the Karasuki manner. He seemed to have determined Charlotte’s high status from her clothes and demeanor.

“Oh my, is that so...” Charlotte recalled how Rio’s parents were immigrants as she observed Gouki’s appearance carefully. His slightly strong accent was probably because he was an immigrant as well. The one thing she was most curious about was how he appeared to be of important status too. His refined movements were clearly ingrained deeply into him, and above all, the sword mastery he showed in the earlier battle was indisputably top class.

How interesting. The mystery around Sir Haruto grows again.

Charlotte smiled in delight, having taken a newfound interest in Gouki’s group.

Incidentally, the reason why Gouki and his people were able to speak the Strahl common tongue was because the Strahl region and Yagumo region once had a select few nations that kept in touch with each other.

Rio also learned this for the first time after meeting Gouki in the Karasuki Kingdom, but there were some nations that used the Strahl common tongue as a second or third official language because of this history, and the Karasuki Kingdom was one such nation.

As it was only considered a second or third official language, it was mostly royals and civil officials that bothered to learn it. Their pronunciation was also rather accented when compared to the standard in Strahl, but Gouki and his people had been studying the language since the moment they decided to follow Rio to Strahl. The heavy accent had greatly improved during their stay in the spirit folk village, but there were still some traces of it.

“Oh, pardon me. My name is Charlotte Galarc, Second Princess of the Galarc Kingdom. Thank you for saving us from the earlier predicament. On behalf of the kingdom, I wish to express my warmest gratitudes.” Charlotte picked up her skirt by the hem and curtsied elegantly.

“Ah, so you’re Princess Charlotte. I’ve heard a lot about you from Sir Haruto.”

“Why, I’m so pleased to hear that. Oh, and allow me to introduce you. This is First Princess Christina and Second Princess Flora from the neighboring kingdom of Beltrum.”

“Hello, I’m Christina. Thank you very much for saving us earlier.”

“I’m her little sister Flora. It’s nice to meet you.”

He must be a soldier who used to serve Sir Amakawa’s mother. From what he showed of his strength, he would have been one of the strongest in the country...

Someone just like the King’s Sword of Beltrum, Alfred Emerle. Since Christina knew that Rio’s mother was royalty, she was able to guess his background more accurately than Charlotte. For someone of such strength to leave Yagumo and come this far, he was probably incredibly loyal to Rio.

Memories of her days at the royal academy flashed through her head, making her frown. Feelings of guilt surged within her. Rio had told her not to worry about it, but these feelings would probably never disappear completely.

“And this is the hero, Lady Satsuki.”

“I’m Sumeragi Satsuki... Ah, that would be Satsuki Sumeragi in this world. It’s very nice to meet you, Gouki.”

Satsuki seemed quite interested in Gouki’s appearance, as he closely resembled a Japanese person, but first gave a simple self-introduction.

“I’ve heard many stories about all of you. It’s very nice to finally be meeting you,” Gouki said, bowing deeply.

“Dear, I’d like to move Lady Alma and Lady Celia to somewhere they can rest.”

Kayoko came up to them with the wounded Alma in her arms. Miharu, Orphia, and Celia were with her.

Celia had been treated terribly by Lucci earlier, but she hadn’t sustained any major wounds or fallen unconscious. Miharu and Orphia had offered to lend her a shoulder to lean on, but she wanted to walk by herself. The only thing she did was cast healing magic on herself just in case.

“In that case, please take her inside the mansion...” Charlotte had just suggested, when—

“A signal flare?” Its light shot across the sky above the castle.

“It isn’t a signal flare from our kingdom,” a nearby knight observed. There were different signal patterns for each kingdom, but she didn’t recognize that one.

“It must belong to the attackers. Their griffin squad must be fleeing,” Charlotte guessed. She could see the mercenaries that had been fighting the aerial knights flying away from the castle.

“I guess they gave up on the mansion...?” Satsuki muttered.

“Everyone has their own post in the battlefield,” Charlotte explained. “Their goal may have been to raid this place, but with the squad in charge wiped out, there’s nothing left for them to do.”

“So they’d abandon their comrades?”

Perhaps she found them heartless, or perhaps she was worried they would return. Either way, it was a question only a novice at war would ask. Her question was answered by Gouki, who was an actual veteran.

“Of course, there’s a possibility they may return, but the role of the enemies in the sky was to secure a path of retreat and prevent reinforcements from arriving. Rushing over here would be the same as abandoning that role. Unless they had a plan that would allow them to rescue their comrades without a path of retreat, they wouldn’t come over here. It’d be the same as an honorable suicide.”

Whether it was in enemy territory or on the front lines, rescuing a comrade was a high-risk action. The rescuing side could end up needing to be rescued themselves, and anyone who left their post could cause the front line to collapse, causing even more damage.

They had to look at the bigger picture. If someone insisted on saving their comrade in spite of that, then they had to make sure there was no issue in leaving their post and keep a path of retreat secured.

It was easy for the side being rescued to unhappily think, “Why didn’t you come to save me?! You’ve gotta be kidding me! Some comrade you are!” but the comrades that had to weigh the risks of rescue were just as easily susceptible to stress and guilt over abandoning their allies. But it was something both sides mutually understood when participating in war. There were even psychological tactics to leave captured enemies alive but powerless on purpose because of this. That was what happened in war.

“I see...” Satsuki looked somber, but seemed to understand.

“If the mercenaries in the sky have begun to flee, then it means there’s no way for them to retrieve their allies. We can leave the rest to the castle guards,” Charlotte stated.

Just then, something roared.

“WROOOOOOH!”

◇ ◇ ◇

Shortly before the signal flare went up in the sky, somewhere in the rooftop garden.

Splendid work. Thank goodness everyone seems to be safe...

King Francois had just witnessed the fight take place outside Rio’s mansion with bated breath. In fact, he was still watching them now. The enemies’ movements had made it clear that their target was Rio’s mansion, but there was another reason he had been so intently focused on the mansion during the entire ordeal.

It began with Celia, Sara, and Alma taking on dozens of monsters by themselves, followed by the fierce attack of the mercenaries that were faster than what the knights with magically enhanced physical abilities could keep up with, followed by the appearance of a huge beast that started to fight the mercenaries for them, followed by Alma getting stabbed, followed by the hero Satsuki coming out of the mansion...

Who was then followed by the princesses stepping out into the garden, followed by the return of the beast that disappeared, followed by the monsters across the castle gathering before the mansion, followed by Celia and Miharu nearly being taken hostage, followed by the arrival of an outrageously strong man and woman from the skies who began overpowering the mercenaries, followed by more people riding a giant bird...

The situation changed more than just once or twice. There was no way he could look away. Even the reports from his subordinates began to get on his nerves, so he left the command of other areas to them from partway through.

I can’t believe they survived an attack of such a scale without any injuries...

There were many things he wanted to confirm as the leader of a nation, but for now, he rejoiced openly.

Those helpers who appeared from the sky are most likely related to Haruto. I can ask the details from him in person when he returns, but I would like to speak to them privately under the pretext of expressing gratitude. Perhaps Charlotte can handle the negotiations.

At that moment, a knight ran up to Francois in a fluster. “The enemy has begun their retreat, Your Majesty! What would you like to do? Shall we pursue them?”

“Go after them, but don’t pursue them too far. Make sure the city is not damaged in the pursuit. Some of the enemies must have been captured already—they will suffice for interrogation. What we should prioritize now is assessing the damages and treating the wounded.”

“Understood. In terms of casualties, there have been a significant number of wounded, but no deaths.”

“Oh? So our military is quite capable after all.” He was tempted to compare them to the people of Rio’s mansion... But regardless of that, he looked pleased.

“The squad in the sky was mostly moving to buy the others time, so things played out well there.”

In addition to that, the castle had many people who were capable of using healing magic. As long as no one was instantly killed in one hit, there were many people available to heal them.

“I see.”

“Also, regarding the matter of their swift movement speed—the secret seems to lie in the swords they had.”

The knight reporting was about to explain the abilities of the enchanted swords the mercenaries were equipped with, when—

“WROOOOOOH!”

It was at that moment that something roared.

Everyone on the rooftop garden flinched in surprise. It almost sounded like the voice was coming from the sky.

“What?!”

Most people looked up reflexively.

“What...is that...?”

What Francois saw was an embodiment of despair.

◇ ◇ ◇

Hero Killer.

It all started over a thousand years ago.

During the era of the Divine War, there was a being that was crowned with the name of Hero Killer for slaughtering countless heroes of the war.

The name of the being that even enchanted-sword-wielding heroes feared was Draugul.

“WROOOOOOH!”

A voice thundered through the capital. It almost sounded like the wailing cry of a man.

The one making the noise wasn’t a revenant left behind on the castle grounds. It wasn’t a griffin in the sky either. Nor was it Ariel, Orphia’s contract spirit that was still in the air. Hel and Ifritah were still in their spirit forms after being wounded earlier. In the first place, it wasn’t a volume of sound that could be made by creatures of their sizes.

“WROOOOOOH!”

The owner of the voice was the Hero Killer, Draugul.

Meanwhile, in the courtyard before Rio’s mansion...

“Hmm. This is a rather strange sight...” Gouki furrowed his brow, looking up at the sky.

“Wh-What is that...?” Satsuki asked, trembling. No one there knew that it was the apparition of the legend. However, if Aishia had been there, she would have been able to associate his presence with Reiss, even if she didn’t know about the Hero Killer Draugul. She had actually fought him once before.

It all took place in Rodania. While Rio was traveling through the Proxia Empire and Paladia Kingdom for information about Lucius, in the middle of Christina and Flora’s abduction taking place elsewhere, Reiss had appeared before Celia. Aishia, who had been guarding her in spirit form, materialized to pursue Reiss, who in turn summoned a large number of monsters and undead knights to fight her.

The Hero Killer was the most powerful of the undead knights Aishia had fought at the time. Unlike the other monsters, he didn’t leave an enchanted gem upon defeat. Reiss had disguised himself as Draugul to fake his death when she defeated him. At the time, the Hero Killer had been deterred by her overwhelming power, but the Hero Killer wasn’t weak by any means.

The era of the Divine War gave birth to many fierce warriors; there was no way someone with a nickname as exaggerated as Hero Killer could be weak. He had earned the title by continuously sending experienced warriors equipped with enchanted swords to their graves. The nickname of Hero Killer was given because it would take the effort of multiple heroes for him to have any chance of defeat.

Minotaurs were dwarfed by the size of his ten-meter-tall body. He wielded a several-meter-long one-handed sword and sturdy-looking shield, on top of being dressed in full body armor. Two wings grew from his back like a devil or fallen angel.

The undead knight glared down from his position a hundred meters in the sky, eyes glinting with ominous hatred. The people inside the capital perceived his presence.

“If the mercenaries in the sky have begun to flee, then it means there’s no way for them to retrieve their allies. We can leave the rest to the castle guards,” Charlotte said.

“Can we leave that to the castle guards too, Char...?” A tense wind blew. Satsuki looked up at the overwhelming presence of Draugul above her head as she nervously questioned Charlotte., but Satsuki hadn’t asked with the intention of mocking the situation. Her expression showed how much she wanted to leave it to the guards if possible.

“Probably not...” Charlotte would have loved nothing more than to agree, but she knew things wouldn’t end well that way. She would have to borrow the strength of the people here to defeat that monster.

“It’s clearly glaring this way. How interesting.” Gouki stared back at the Hero Killer in the sky with a smirk.

“N-No, no it’s not! It isn’t interesting at all!” Satsuki shouted in protest.

“Leave this to me. Since we don’t know how it will move, it would be best for everyone here to focus on defending with barriers.”

“It sounds like you’re planning on charging in alone, but I’m going to fight too, dear.” Kayoko lined up alongside Gouki, who was raring to fight.

Gouki looked at his wife and grinned. “Hmm... Fine. But don’t think your excitement is being hidden right now.”

“Of course not. This is the perfect situation to test our worth in Sir Haruto’s absence. It’s only natural to feel spirited, wouldn’t you agree?”

“It is indeed. We will express our devotion for Sir Haruto by protecting everyone here. It truly feels like I’m swinging my sword for him. Bring the monster on! I couldn’t have asked for a more worthy opponent!”

Gouki pointed his katana at the sky and yelled fiercely.

While the fearsome roar and sinister aura of the being had clutched everyone else’s hearts with despair, Gouki and Kayoko showed no hesitation at all. In fact, their unfazed attitudes spurred on the others around them.

“I will fight too!” Sara stated first.

“As will I.”

“And me, of course.”

Celia and Orphia added.

“No no, you should all focus on defending yourselves. Sir Haruto isn’t here right now,” Gouki said, hurriedly encouraging them to retract their offers.

“That’s exactly why!”

“Yup!”

Sara and Orphia were unyielding.

“Hrmm...”

“It’s precisely because Haruto is absent right now that we have to work together to overcome this dilemma. If I let someone else protect me here, I’ll become someone who always needs to be protected by Haruto... I want to prove that I don’t need to be protected. I don’t want Haruto to distance himself because of my own weakness!” Celia said. She conveyed the same feelings she had before Lucci and the mercenaries here, in front of the Hero Killer.

“Lady Aishia is the only one who can truly fight together with him, after all. Even if the two of them were here right now, Haruto would leave Lady Aishia behind to protect us and fight alone. But that’s so lonely for him, and somewhat frustrating for us.”

“We know he’s acting for our sakes, but we want him to rely on us a little more.”

“Yes!”

Sara and Orphia confessed their true thoughts as though to encourage themselves. At any rate, they had presented their motives for fighting. There was no need for further discussion.

Just like how Gouki and Kayoko saw the situation as a chance to prove their loyalty to Rio, the girls wanted to put up a proper fight in Rio and Aishia’s absence.

“The elderly shouldn’t dismiss the hearts of young ladies so lightly, dear.”

“Hmm... I’m reminded of all the times Lady Ayame made such ridiculous requests.” The feelings of the three girls had affected him.

“Either way, Ariel’s presence will be indispensable in an aerial battle against that thing. Let us borrow their strength gratefully,” Kayoko advised.

“All right, I understand. Let us defeat him together.”

Thus, they all found their resolution.

“Protection of the ground will be handled by Miharu, Ifritah, and Hel. The two spirits will put up essence barriers, so could you supply them with magic essence? Offense isn’t the only means of fighting. It’s an important role only you can fill.”

If they were going to fight the Hero Killer Draugul, they couldn’t just focus on attacking. Sara nominated Miharu as the key to their defense for her ample amounts of magic essence.

“Sure, leave it to me.”

Miharu couldn’t imagine herself fighting the enemy that had appeared in the sky. She’d just be helpless and get in the way of others. The somewhat lonely expression on her face was because of how keenly she felt her current limits. However, that didn’t mean she had nodded weakly. She wanted to do what she was capable of, so she spoke up with a firm voice.

“The mercenaries might use this chance to attack again. Latifa and Satsuki will be in charge of suppressing them! Please guard the others, you two!” Sara said, leaving an order for Latifa and Satsuki as well.

“Okay!”

“Got it...!”

The two of them braced themselves and nodded.

“...” Meanwhile, the Hero Killer was still looking down at the ground brazenly.

“Why doesn’t it come down to the ground...?” Flora wondered out loud. Indeed, it could descend if it wanted to.

“Like the monsters that appeared earlier, it’s clearly there to support the mercenaries. I don’t know how it’s possible, but someone in the Heavenly Lions is clearly controlling these monsters from the shadows. In which case, they might not want to hit their comrades on the ground,” Christina guessed, looking around at her surroundings. There hadn’t been enough time to gather all the unconscious mercenaries in one spot, so they were scattered about everywhere. If the Hero Killer descended right now, they would be affected by the battle, and she assumed he didn’t want that to happen.

At any rate, it was impossible to predict how the apparition would move. There was no telling how long this silence would continue for. They didn’t know how he would attack, and they didn’t know if there was another reason why he wasn’t attacking. They had an overwhelming lack of information.

But they had to make a choice.

“We wouldn’t want it to fight beside Sir Haruto’s mansion and destroy it either. I’d like to make the first move against it...” Gouki said, presenting his first choice.

“Right. Orphia, please lend us Ariel.”

“Go ahead! And Celia, use this to recover your magic essence.”

The whole party climbed onto the giant bird’s back, including Orphia herself. While doing so, she handed a spirit stone to Celia. Celia recognized what it was right away. “Thank you!”

After keeping up a barrier for so long in the earlier battle, Celia was completely out of essence. Partway through the battle, she had started to draw essence from the spirit stone Rio had previously given her, but she appreciated the extra boost to her recovery.

“All right, here we go!”

With Gouki’s shout, Ariel rose into the sky. Then, as though it had been waiting for that moment—

“WRRROOOOOOH!”

Like a fallen angel hovering in the sky, the undead knight howled loud enough to shake the air over the capital.

“Orphia and I will use long-ranged attacks to watch how it reacts first,” Celia offered, exchanging looks with Orphia.

“Understood. Kayoko and I will handle the close-range combat, along with Lady Sara.”

It was their specialty style of fighting, after all. The division of roles was decided swiftly.

“For now, I’ll use intermediate-level magic to gain the advantage in attack numbers. Orphia will watch the opponent while preparing a big attack!”

“Okay!”

“Septet Magi: Magicae Displodo!”

Seven magic circles appeared above Ariel’s head. One beat later, seven beams of light fired out of them. Each cannon shot that was fired like a greeting had enough force to knock out a warrior physically enhanced with an enchanted sword.

He’s not moving out of the way?

The Hero Killer made no move to evade.

“...”

He calmly raised his shield at the incoming barrage.

“Wha— You’ve gotta be kidding me...” Celia was dumbfounded as the fifth, then sixth shot met its target. He staggered a little in the air, but he was continuously taking intermediate-level cannon fire from in front without issue.

Eventually, Celia’s seventh shot met its mark.

“I’m ready!” Orphia fired a single arrow of light from Ariel’s back. All the magic essence she would have used on flying was able to be refined for her attack, making her arrow much more powerful that Celia’s cannon fire.

“Wruuuh!” Instead of raising his shield to block the attack, the Hero Killer swung his shield to knock the arrow down. As a result, he didn’t sustain any damage.

“I see... He seems to be rather confident in his defense. But the attack just now had enough force to require him to knock it away with the shield instead,” Gouki said, analyzing his movements.

Orphia’s one attack had the same amount of force as advanced-level magic. If I want to damage him, I’ll have to use advanced-level offensive magic too.

Celia immediately began to consider the candidates for her next attack spell.

“In that case, that shield and armor will be quite the nuisance,” Kayoko said, sighing in annoyance.

“Yes. Anything fired from afar will be blocked by that shield. And I’m sure he can evade if he needs to as well.”

Sara also realized the high difficulty of defeating him from afar and frowned. During that time, Ariel rose until it was higher than the Hero Killer.

“At any rate, we’ve now obtained information about his defenses. He’s also shown how he responds to long-ranged attacks. Which leaves the matter of close-range combat! Now, it’s my turn to test his reactions!” Gouki leaped down from Ariel’s back and ran through the air towards the Hero Killer. His opponent sensed his approach and made eye contact with him.

“...”

“Ha ha! He’s even bigger up close!” The Hero Killer was easily ten times Gouki’s size, but Gouki just laughed heartily as he charged forward.

The first one to swing their weapon was the Hero Killer. The one-handed sword was several meters long, so its reach was on a different level to Gouki’s. However, Gouki understood that clearly as he continued charging.

Good reaction speed, and precise aim! His speed is also impressive, but...

Gouki jumped midair and evaded the attack. The Hero Killer’s sword swung under him, missing. The wind pressure pushed his body upwards.

“Let’s see how sturdy those weak points of your defense are!”

Gouki weaved through the gap between helmet and armor, aiming for the Hero Killer’s neck. However, his opponent wasn’t about to allow that so easily. The Hero Killer swung his shield upwards in an attempt to knock Gouki back.

“Whoa! That shield really is a nuisance!”

Gouki used his comparatively smaller frame to his advantage and evaded the attack. He then made a temporary retreat to where Ariel was.

“His reaction speed and movement speed aren’t impossible to keep up with, but that giant body and equipment are a huge problem. His defenses are too strong. If we were to bring him down with long-ranged attacks, I could run around and distract him from lifting his shield. That may be the best way of getting a powerful hit in,” he said to the others.

“An alternative would be for Orphia and I to blow away that shield so that you can all get a hit in where the body is uncovered by armor,” Celia suggested.

“Ha ha, that sounds equally exhilarating. The thought of cutting down such a huge and solid body makes my heart dance. However, he’s yet to show a true weakness. We’ll need to observe him while fighting a little more to find his weak points!” Gouki said, then ran off to challenge the Hero Killer again.

“I’ll go too.”

“I’m going as well!”

Kayoko and Sara jumped off Ariel and followed him. Thus, the battle between five fierce warriors and the Hero Killer commenced for real.

Chapter 6: Tachi of Wind

Shortly before the Hero Killer appeared in the sky, Arein’s aerial stalling squad had just begun to retreat from the castle at the signal flare.

“Run for it! No one’s saving you if you get caught!” Arein shouted, hurrying his comrades from the rear of the group.

Shit... We sacrificed so much, and yet...

They were being forced to retreat without capturing any hostages. With no results to show for the price they paid, this was an utter defeat.

The raid on the Galarc Castle had started with fifty people, but there were less than half of them able to retreat. They had lost over twenty-five of their capable comrades, along with all the fake enchanted swords they had been equipped with. It was a huge loss for the Heavenly Lions. Unable to do anything about it, Arein scowled.

If we could at least retrieve the guys in the mansion...

There was no guarantee they were still alive, but he had witnessed the knights capturing their comrades just before they began their retreat.

However, there was no doubt retrieval would be difficult. Their initial surprise attack had succeeded thanks to the use of monsters that sent the castle security into disarray. Reiss had also provided assistance from the air for a while. But the more time that passed since the attack began, the more of the Galarc Castle’s army was dispatched for battle. Even if they charged back with their entire group, they’d just be surrounded and beat up one-sidedly.

In fact, the aerial knights of the Galarc Kingdom were pursuing them right this moment, from a distance of several dozens of meters away.

There’s no choice but to abandon them... Arein repeated to convince himself.

But just then—

“WROOOOOOH!”

The air across the capital trembled.

“Whoa! Whoa, there!”

Arein flinched in shock, as did the griffin he was riding. It lost its balance in midair and wavered.

“Wh...What is that...?”

At that moment, both the fleeing mercenaries and pursuing aerial knights completely forgot about each other. They were all distracted by the undead knight that appeared above their heads.

“Is that Reiss’s work as well? He didn’t mention anything about such a huge monster in the strategy meeting before the attack...”

The undead knight in the sky, the Hero Killer, was an irregular being for Arein and the mercenary squad as well. But they already knew who was controlling the monsters in this attack.

“I don’t get it, but our pursuers are faltering. This is our chance to get away!” Arein recovered immediately and focused on their escape. Fortunately, the army dispatched by the castle stopped pursuing them there, fearing further damage to the castle.

Thus, they completed their escape from the capital a few minutes later. They descended at a spring in the forest on the outskirts of the capital—the same place they had agreed on gathering after the operation. The moment they alighted from their griffins, exhaustion swept over them. They sat down in silence and sighed tiredly.

“Hmm. Your numbers have decreased a lot.” Reiss descended beside them, looking around at their numbers and commenting out loud.

“Mister Reiss...”

“I am aware you were unable to accomplish the goal.”

“...” The first thing that came to Arein’s mind was an excuse, which he swallowed with a bitter expression. The others around them had similar faces as they looked on in silence.

“I have no intention of criticizing you. You, your squad, and the squads in charge of the mansion all worked well. There were a total of fifty mercenaries equipped with enchanted swords. Of this number, twenty-five were sent to the mansion, which is quite a considerable force. Enough to launch an effective surprise attack on the royal castle of a major power. That’s why I thought there was enough power on our side, but my judgment was incorrect. The strength of those at the mansion caught me by surprise. As did the reinforcements.”

Reiss lifted his palms and shrugged as though to say he was at a loss for what to do.

“Because of that, I had no choice but to bring that thing out.”

He looked in the direction of the royal capital. Gouki’s group was fighting the Hero Killer in the sky.

“So that was your doing as well?”

“Yes,” Reiss said, nodding.

“...” He was unable to voice any criticisms, but Arein’s expression was clearly protesting why Reiss didn’t bring out a powerful monster earlier if he had such a strong card up his sleeve from the beginning. Reiss must have read that question from his face, as he began to explain.

“It wasn’t my intention to let that thing fight here. I have suffered a considerable loss by bringing it out as well.”

Namely, giving Rio the ability to determine that Reiss was still alive.

Reiss had already informed Arein and his men that he had faked his death before Rio and Aishia, but he hadn’t explained that it was done by making Aishia think he was the Hero Killer and having her defeat him. That’s why he didn’t specify what it was he had lost in this situation.

“So why did you...?” Arein asked.

“The raid this time has taught me something important—that the Black Knight has surrounded himself with capable people. If we cannot secure a hostage, then we should at least remove some of those annoyances. The other reason is because I have a favor to ask of you.”

“A favor?”

“The enchanted sword Lucci wielded was an important memento of your commander. I’m sure you would want to retrieve it as well, no? And so, we’re going to retrieve both Lucci and his sword right now.”

Reiss revealed the details of his favor.

“N-No way. I mean, I’d love to do so if I could, but going back now is just asking for the people in the castle to snipe us down! Even with that monster in the air, they’re going to be on the watch for a second attack!”

They would be heading straight for their deaths, Arein argued back.

“I’m not asking you to charge in headfirst. Take this...” Reiss took out a sparkling gemstone from his breast pocket.

“This is...”

“You should be familiar with its use, no? It’s a single-use teleport crystal. It will take you right beside the mansion. And this one is for your escape.”

“When did you...?”

“Lucci was being pushed into a rather disadvantageous position, so I snuck through the chaos and set up the teleport coordinates as a backup.”

“I see. Nothing gets past you,” Arein muttered in awe.

“I’ve ordered that thing to focus on fighting in the air, so all their main forces will be directed to the sky right now. The mansion should be shorthanded right about now,” Reiss said with a smirk.

“Can I save the others inside as well...?”

“As you know, the maximum number of people that can be moved by single-use teleport crystals is six. It will be impossible to retrieve everyone. As long as you keep that in mind, I don’t mind what you do. However, the highest priority is Lucci and Lucius’s sword. If you let your greed get the best of you, this teleport crystal will not only be wasted, it’ll fall into enemy hands and be abused for their benefit. Please understand that.”

Reiss placed emphasis on his warning, not wanting the plan to fail.

“I understand... I’ll do it. I have no reason not to. I’ll form an assault squad immediately.”

Sure enough, Arein accepted the teleport crystal from him.

◇ ◇ ◇

Meanwhile, in the skies above the capital, Gouki and the others were locked in a cutthroat battle with Draugul. Gouki, Kayoko, and Sara were using the sky as the front line, surrounding the Hero Killer. He specialized in close combat, and his power, speed, and abilities as a swordsman were exceptionally high across the board.

“He has a high degree of skill as a swordsman. His use of the shield to defend is also top class. Above all, he has a solid build. Breaking through from the front is near impossible. It may be better to focus on merely distracting him,” said Gouki, who was challenging Draugul from the front. The Hero Killer engaged them in large-scale melee combat, making good use of his sword and shield while staying faithful to the basic fighting forms. He didn’t seem to have any means of long-ranged attack, but by simply swinging his shield, he was able to create a violent storm.

“Raaargh!” His sword swings also disturbed the wind with its aftermath.

“Hah!” Gouki made several jumps in midair, evading the areas with wild winds. It was at that moment that Sara made a move, having snuck around to the Hero Killer’s side.

“Haaah!”

Her dagger was within reach of the Hero Killer’s helmet. The next moment, his head had frozen over, turned into a giant block of ice. However...

“Rah...!” However, the Hero Killer didn’t falter. He didn’t stop moving. He shot his arm up to swipe Sara away from his face. Sara leaped on the spur of the moment and distanced herself. But the Hero Killer’s frozen head didn’t seem to change his field of view. That was how much precision was packed into the swing that chased her.

“Ugh... Where are the eyes on that thing? Jeez!” This time, Sara leaped vertically to evade the strike. She rode the wind created by the huge sword passing under her and spun in the air, shouting.

“Take that!”

Orphia, who was now flying by herself, successively fired thick arrows of light. Each one had the force of an intermediate-level offensive spell, but they all had a homing effect that focused on the frozen head of Draugul. However, he was an iron wall that didn’t even flinch over a spell of intermediate level. The Hero Killer twisted his huge body and swung his shield, mowing down the light arrows over an extensive range. But the arrows weren’t the main point.

“Magnus Magicae Displodo!” Riding on Ariel’s back, Celia fired the extra-large magic essence cannon she had prepared at Draugul’s frozen head. It was a simple but powerful advanced-level spell that had the same force as all the arrows Orphia just fired added together.

However, her opponent was still able to see every attack. He bent his upper body to easily evade the shot.

“In that case...!” Kayoko used the kodachi she held in both hands to release a water whip, wrapping around the Hero Killer’s neck. She then yanked on them with all her might, pulling him off balance ever so slightly.

“Gouki!”

“On it! Hidden Skill, Second Blade, Aura Mico!”

Gouki had made his way behind the enemy in the blink of an eye, closing the thirty-meter distance to slash at the Hero Killer’s back.

The cuts of wind his secret art created were packed with power, and the slashes caused the Hero Killer’s body to fall forward. The armor on his back cracked faintly, which didn’t escape Gouki’s notice.

“I will provide support!”

The moment where Draugul lost his balance was their biggest chance. Orphia immediately began rapid-firing additional light arrows, this time hitting his head with all of them.

“Haaaaaah!”

Sara had also sent magic essence to turn her dagger into a two-meter-long blade of ice, slamming it down on his head from above. The Hero Killer’s head jerked downwards.

“This time it’ll work! Magnus Magicae Displodo!” Celia had gone around to the front to directly land the second shot of her extra-large essence cannon. Cracks spread across the entire armor as Draugul was knocked back from his forward-bending position.

“Yay!”

Everyone cheered, thinking they had landed an effective hit on him.

“Raaagh!” However, the Hero Killer used the momentum of the knockback to flap his wings and rise.

“What?!” Gouki shouted, shocked by how vigorously he moved. Everyone was dumbfounded by his impressive show of endurance.

“But I saw there were cracks in the helmet and armor! If we can hit him one more time with an attack like just now...!” Sara said hopefully.

“Great idea, but it seems he’s wary of us now!” Gouki warned with a grim look.

Now that he knew that they had attacks that could break through his defenses, the Hero Killer was flying around at a distance to them. His flying speed was fairly fast—too fast for them to keep up unless they were able to fly freely like Orphia or Ariel.

“It’s hard to land our attacks when he’s moving that fast. And he’s too dangerous to approach recklessly...”

Orphia’s arrows of light were being evaded with ease.

“H-His helmet and armor... It’s repairing itself!” Sara shouted in shock.

Orphia nodded nervously. “Yeah, you’re right.”

Like Sara said, the equipment on the Hero Killer was rapidly repairing itself in front of her eyes. It wasn’t instant, but it was happening fast enough for it to be fully repaired in less than a minute.

They probably had to damage the skeleton body in order to defeat him, but now they had to start from cracking the sturdy armor and helmet all over again. On top of that, he was constantly keeping his distance from them, giving his armor time to repair.

“Something that big, solid, and fast can regenerate itself? That’s not fair...”

What could they do about it? Despair and panic filled Celia’s face. It was only natural for her to be at a loss—no one there was aware, but many heroes had fallen to this regenerative iron wall in the Divine War.

“He’s more troublesome than I imagined...” Kayoko muttered, glaring at the Hero Killer circling in the air with great force.

“RAAAAAAH!”

The Hero Killer changed trajectories and charged towards Celia. His helmet and armor had fully repaired itself, and he was armed with his shield that was far sturdier than the armor.

“Ngh!”

Gouki, Kayoko, Sara, Orphia, and Ariel, with Celia on its back, all scattered in different directions. The Hero Killer focused on Gouki, chasing after him without a second look at the others.

There was no human that could survive a tackle by such a large being, physically enhanced body or not.

“Whoa! This is quite the predicament!” Gouki waited until the last moment before successfully evading the charge. He watched his retreating back with a grim look.

“Everyone, let’s all group up with Ariel for now! The situation will only get worse like this! Save your essence and stamina!” Orphia shouted at Gouki, Kayoko, and Sara. “Ariel, get everyone!”

Ariel moved towards Kayoko, Sara, then Gouki, to retrieve them in that order. Finally, Orphia climbed onto its back.

“The enemy has a huge frame on top of all that speed. It may be difficult to attack him from every direction like before...” Gouki glared at the Hero Killer as it circled.

“I don’t suppose he’ll just fly away like that, will he...?” Celia murmured with a despaired look.

“He’s clearly aiming for us, after all. Fortunately, he’s shown no sign of heading for the ground, but there’s no guarantee this will continue forever. We need to defeat him as soon as possible, but he’s quite the formidable enemy. This is bad.”

In contrast to his words, Gouki had a fierce grin on his face, watching the Hero Killer.

“You don’t look very troubled...” Sara muttered with a sigh.

“He’s just a war nut, so don’t worry about him. He’ll come up with a ridiculous plan sooner or later, so give him a minute.”

Kayoko reassured the others, completely used to his behavior. At the same time, she showed deep trust in the strategies Gouki came up with.

Hmm. His body is covered in sturdy armor, and he constantly has his shield up. In order to defeat him, we have to destroy those and smash his skeleton body, but we haven’t been able to scratch the shield so far. The helmet and armor seem breakable, but they repair over time. Which means we have to deal even more damage than before, outpace the repair speed of the helmet and armor, then break his body... But he flies so fast, it’ll be a real challenge.

In reality, the strategy for defeating the Hero Killer was extremely simple. What Aishia had previously done was close in on the Hero Killer at a faster speed than he could fly around, then use one heavy attack to break everything before it could repair.

But that simplicity was what was most difficult.

If I use my secret arts in succession, I should be able to do enough damage to break the armor and body. In order to do that, his movements have to be stopped. Hmm...

The problem was how to stop the nimble movements of such a monster so that the secret arts could hit their target. Gouki considered the possibilities.

The best time to attack would be when he attacks us... But he’s especially confident in his use of the shield to defend his front. He’d ignore any superficial attacks to charge straight for us. Wait, no. I see. He charges forward when...

It was at that point that Gouki had a light bulb moment.

“I have an idea,” he proposed with a grin.

◇ ◇ ◇

Miharu and the others on the ground watched the fight taking place from in front of the mansion. They were protected by Hel and Ifritah, who had set up a two-layered barrier around them.

The Hero Killer had shown no sign of wanting to descend to the ground, so the group appeared to be safe within the barrier. The commander of Charlotte’s knights, Louise, looked around at her surroundings and reached the same conclusion.

“Princess Charlotte, I believe now would be a good time to restrain the mercenaries lying around,” Louise suggested.

The Hero Killer had appeared shortly after the mercenaries were defeated, so there were still a number of them lying around without any restraints. They hadn’t even finished retrieving the enchanted swords that were in the mercenaries’ possession. While some of the mercenaries had received fatal wounds, there were others who were merely passed out. If they regained consciousness and started attacking again, things could get dicey.

“Indeed. Can you handle that yourself?” But just as Charlotte nodded in agreement, a dozen or so of the castle’s knights approached the mansion.

“Princess Charlotte!”

“They’re finally here,” Charlotte muttered weakly, watching the approaching knights.

“This is...”

The knights that came running to them took one look around at the surroundings and fell speechless. The aftermath of a fierce battle spread around them—unconscious mercenaries lying on the desolate ground, enchanted gems left behind from the revenants, and a crater caused by Orphia’s attack.

At the center of the disastrous spectacle was Charlotte’s group, protected by a barrier of light. Two huge beasts in the shape of Hel and Ifritah stood beside them, so it was only natural they’d fall speechless at such a sight.

“Perfect timing. Cooperate with them. Lady Satsuki and Lady Latifa will protect us, as will these two here.” Charlotte looked up at Hel and Ifritah to confirm that it wouldn’t be a problem, then gave Louise her orders. Louise immediately replied with an affirmative.

“Hel, Ifritah. Can you make a hole in the barrier for the knights to leave?” Miharu asked the two mid-class spirits.

“Gruuuh!” Her words seemed to have reached them, as a hole large enough to fit two or three people opened at the front of the barrier.

“I’ll be going, then...”

Louise gave Hel and Ifritah a curious glance before heading out of the barrier. She then went around with the knights to restrain the mercenaries and prepare for them to be sent to the castle dungeons. No one noticed the group of people watching them from the shadows nearby.

◇ ◇ ◇

Meanwhile, in the skies overhead...

“I have an idea,” Gouki began.

“Wow, Kayoko was right.”

“Indeed.”

Sara and Orphia commented in admiration.

“So what’s the plan, Gouki?” Celia asked hopefully. She seemed to find Gouki’s unshakable personality very reliable in a situation such as this, as she had the mindset to let out a small giggle.

“About that. Do you have an attack spell that would be effective against him, Lady Celia?” Gouki asked. “If you have a powerful spell up your sleeve, I’d like you to drive it into him and weaken him...”

There was one spell that came to Celia’s mind. “I do. It’s stronger than the cannon fire magic I cast earlier, and it’s the strongest spell in my arsenal. But I only have enough essence to cast it once. Whether I can hit him when he moves around like that is...”

She wasn’t confident.

“You only need to hit him once. As long as we can make sure that one spell hits, it won’t be a problem.”

“R-Right. But how can we make sure...?”

The opponent they were up against was no pushover, but Celia nodded first and waited for the rest of Gouki’s idea.

“If it’s just for a brief moment, then I have a means of moving fast enough to match his speed. I’ll first aim an attack directly at his front, reducing his speed. That should make it easier to hit him with magic. If you use that chance to hit him, you can buy us some time.”

“I understand...”

“Lady Sara, Lady Orphia, and Kayoko’s cooperation will also be essential. Lady Sara and Lady Orphia, are you able to create water whips like Kayoko’s in order to restrain him?”

“It might be difficult if he’s moving around. I’m not too sure about it. If the three of us release whips at the same time, we might be able to restrain him, but I don’t think it’d take much for him to break free with his strength...”

Sara and Orphia exchanged expressions of uncertainty.

“You’ll be restraining him after Lady Celia casts her magic, so his movements should be slowed somewhat. If the three of you could use that opening to restrain him enough to prevent him from flying away, that would be great.”

“Right, that should be manageable,” Sara said, nodding with more confidence.

“Then the next step is to pass him and make him face a different direction. Lady Orphia, can you ask Ariel to adjust its flight path?”

“I can. Ariel,” Orphia called. Ariel began to circle around.

“Now then, I will be the vanguard, so I’m counting on you all to activate your techniques at the right time.”

“Roger that!”

They had no intention of losing. They wouldn’t have come up to the sky in the first place if they had. That’s why the group all nodded firmly at Gouki’s instructions.

Thus, the five heroes resumed their battle with the Hero Killer.

“I’m going to prepare the spell. Wait one moment.”

First, Celia began her preparations to cast the spell for the plan. The Claire family had a secret attack spell that was passed down through the generations. This secret spell was the magic Celia was about to use.

In terms of modern magic, the spell would be categorized in the highest grade. It was a super spell that could only be cast by those of Claire blood with exceptional magical talent.

“Aperio: Caelestis Magicus,” Celia murmured, creating a magic circle that wrapped around her. “Verifico: Celia Claire.”

The magic circle wrapping around her glowed brighter.

“Salvatio Initium.”

The magic circle condensed around her right arm.

“Impetus...”

She then cast an extra spell to provide the necessary magic essence for activation. In response, all the magic essence within her began to gather in her right arm. Magic essence was normally unable to be seen by anyone who couldn’t cast spirit arts, but the essence had condensed so much, destructive energy was visibly flowing from her arm before being activated.

Gouki’s eyes widened at the sight of Celia’s right arm. “That looks like quite the tremendous spell you’re preparing,” he commented

Celia nodded with a strained expression. “I believe I’ll be able to meet your expectations—as long as it hits, that is.”

“That’s amazing...” Orphia muttered, staring at Celia’s arm.

“Yes... I wouldn’t want to handle essence this close to exploding. In fact, I can’t,” Sara agreed, forehead breaking into a cold sweat.

“It’s taking all I have to control the essence. Every other task is entrusted to the spell formula...”

All Celia was doing right now was controlling the magic essence. The majority of the other tasks required to activate the magic were left to the spell formula so that all her processing ability could focus on essence control. A spirit arts user would have had to perform all those tasks by themselves, so entrusting such things to the spell formula was something that could only be done with magic.

Thus, after a few long seconds...

“Mora... I’m done preparing. All that’s left is to chant the spell and the magic will activate. Whenever you’re ready,” Celia said, having finally completed her preparation to activate the magic.

“Thank you. Seeing your spell has helped me refocus my mind,” Gouki said to Celia, then glanced at Orphia. “Now, if you would do the honors, Lady Orphia.”

“We just need to charge straight at him, right?”

“Indeed! Please do!”

“Got it. Ariel!”

“Kreeeh!” At Orphia’s signal, Ariel changed direction. Until now, it had been flying in circles around the Hero Killer to maintain a distance, but it now backed away in order to make a direct approach.

Ten-odd seconds later, Ariel was glaring at the Hero Killer from a distance of a hundred meters.

“Wruuuh!” The Hero Killer seemed to have sensed Ariel’s incoming charge. With full confidence in his own defenses, he lifted his shield and accelerated towards them as though to accept their challenge. At this point, there were only a few dozen meters left between them.

“Kreeeh!” Meanwhile, Ariel was normally surrounded by a wind barrier to keep its passengers from feeling any wind resistance during flight. Under such conditions, Gouki was able to stand and draw his katana.

“Now, here I go!” Gouki said with a light leap. A strong wind blew softly at his back—and the next moment, Gouki was accelerating through the sky, leaving Ariel behind him.

“So fast!” Sara was shocked.

“Is that Haruto’s technique for moving at high speeds?” Orphia asked, guessing at the theory behind his high-speed movement with wide eyes. High-speed movement with wind spirit arts was Rio’s specialty.

My acceleration isn’t as skillful as Sir Rio’s, but yes. All I can do is charge forward in a straight line, thanks to Lord Dominic forging Kamaitachi for me!

That’s right—by equipping his beloved blade Kamaitachi, Gouki was able to obtain the technique for accelerating in one go.

His technique was still rough compared to Rio’s, but he was still able to imitate him. Perhaps it was because he had fallen in love at first sight with the technique after Rio used it against him, and had continuously imagined himself using it ever since. Or perhaps it was the result of all his loyalty towards Rio.

“Hidden Skill, First Blade, Aura Vulnus!”

Gouki was already within a dozen meters of the Hero Killer, sending a slashing attack of wind diagonally upwards to the right. His might was far beyond what he had demonstrated to Rio in the Karasuki Kingdom.

“AAAAARH!”

The huge frame of the Hero Killer that was protected by his shield decelerated dramatically. It still wasn’t enough to damage him.

“Hidden Skill, Second Blade, Aura Mico!”

At that moment, Gouki turned his katana and stepped even closer to the undead knight. He charged into his decelerated opponent and aimed another attack at the shield, this time making direct contact with the surface. The Hero Killer decelerated further.

“This mass sure is a struggle to overpower! I cannot even crack the shield... But he’s slowed down a good amount. Now, Lady Celia!” Gouki yelled at Celia behind him. Ariel flew forwards, approaching the Hero Killer. As it passed by, Celia swung her right arm with the magic circle around it like a sword.

“Durandal!”

This was the secret spell of the Count Claire family. The condensed magic essence was released as pure destructive energy, attempting to mow down the enemy before them.

“RAAAAAH!” The Hero Killer must have sensed the threat of Celia’s magic, as he desperately tried to brace his shield for the attack.

“TAKE THAT!” Celia roared.

“WRAAAAAAAAH!”

The shield that hadn’t even chipped until now shattered into pieces. In fact, half of the body that had been holding the shield was gone, armor and all.

The highest grade of attack magic normally focused on expanding the area of its attack range as much as possible, but Celia’s Durandal magic focused on condensing the power into as small of a range as possible. As a result, the iron wall of the Hero Killer, which had withstood numerous attacks from heroes during the Divine War, was blown away.

“A-Amazing! That’s incredible, Celia!”

“Yeah!”

Sara and Orphia cheered in spite of themselves.

“Th-That’s all...I’ve got...” Celia weakly collapsed against Ariel’s back.

“As expected of Sir Rio’s teacher. Splendid work, Lady Celia. I doubt there’s even a need for us anymore, but a job is a job.” Kayoko released the water whip from her kodachi.

“Wait, it’s our turn, Sara!”

“R-Right!”

Sara and Orphia created water whips in their hands and used them to grasp the Hero Killer’s body.

“RAAAAAH!” With half his body gone and the rest of his body restrained, the Hero Killer toppled off balance midair, exactly as they planned.

“Ha ha, well done indeed! You’ve made my job much easier now. However, that would be discourteous to this warrior, no matter how much of a monster he may be. I shall assist in putting him out of his misery with my hidden skill!” Gouki made a huge leap midair, rushing at the Hero Killer once more with his katana held over his head. By imitating Rio’s movement techniques, he accelerated as he approached.

“Hidden Skill, First Blade, Aura Vulnus!”

A diagonal slashing attack flew towards the undead knight. In his unbalanced state, the Hero Killer was unable to swing his sword fast enough and took the hit directly to his chestplate.

“Hidden Skill, Second Blade, Aura Mico!”

Then, Gouki accelerated even further, swinging his katana to release a diagonal slashing attack in the opposite direction. When the two attacks overlapped with each other, the undead knight’s armor completely shattered, causing him to roar in pain.

“GRAAAH!”

But he had still yet to die.

“Then take this! Hidden Skill, Third Blade, Aura Vacuo!” With his katana swung the whole way through, Gouki made a following horizontal slash, dividing the Hero Killer’s ribcage into two.

“...” Not even the Hero Killer could survive that. Both his body and the sword in his hand disintegrated into the air.

“Looks like the Fourth Blade wasn’t needed.” Gouki sheathed his katana cleanly, then returned to Ariel’s back.

Not long after, cheers shook the Galarc Kingdom’s capital. It was the voices of the citizens who had watched the battle take place in the sky. A hymn of victory.

Afterword

Hello everyone, this is Yuri Kitayama. Thank you for reading Seirei Gensouki: Spirit Chronicles volume 19—Tachi of Wind.

So, volume 19 has been released! I believe most of you are reading this afterword after the story, but I’ve also heard that some people like to read from the afterword, so I’ll try to refrain from giving too many spoilers.

Now, to start, Rio has a tendency to fight alone too much. Part of the reason is because he has too much power, but his personality that prevents him from getting others involved also plays a big part.

The people who normally spend their time around him naturally understand that, but I hoped to depict how they accepted that, how they wanted to live with that, and what kind of growth they go through!

In the upcoming volume 20, there’ll be plenty of action around Rio and Aishia based on the developments of volume 19.

Just like how volume 10 was a big turning point for the story, volume 20 will also bring about big developments...or so I hope, so please look forward to the release!

As always, there’s a preview of the next volume at the end of this book, so check that out. The subtitle will be “Her Crusade.”

Next, information about the anime series has started being released bit by bit. The latest news can be found on the official website, Seirei Gensouki’s official Twitter, and occasionally on my own Twitter. Please follow them if you’re interested!

There are still many things I can’t tell you, but I believe the anime of Seirei Gensouki will be wonderful.

As the author, I’m cooperating with the production wherever I can, and I can keenly feel the professionalism of everyone every day.

And so, I hope you’ll look forward to both volume 20 of the novel and the anime series! Let’s enjoy the show together once it broadcasts!

Finally, I extend my deepest gratitude to the readers and everyone involved! Let us meet again in volume 20!

Yuri Kitayama

March 2021

Epilogue

Three days after the attack by the Heavenly Lions, in the afternoon, King Francois of Galarc was visiting Rio’s mansion for the first time since the attack.

Part of the reason was to hear the testimonies of the residents, but he had already received an advance report of that from Charlotte, who gathered the necessary information immediately after the attack. The biggest reason for his visit was to thank those who contributed the most to repelling the insurgents and meet Gouki’s group for the first time.

The reason for the wait was related to the reason why Francois was visiting the mansion in person instead of summoning them to the castle.

The battle with the Hero Killer Draugul had been witnessed across the capital, including by those in the castle. It was clear that summoning them to the castle immediately after the fight would result in meddling nobles attempting to make contact.

However, much of the information in Charlotte’s report was better kept confidential. Releasing the information carelessly could result in provoking antipathy from Satsuki or Rio, which was undesirable for Francois as well. There were also some matters he wanted to obtain Rio’s consent for when releasing the information. Waiting before the visit also allowed him to buy time before Rio’s return, which was why Francois was only visiting after three days.

Incidentally, Sara and Gouki had not revealed all their secrets to the Galarc Kingdom. For example, they had explained the existence of spirit arts and how Hel, Ifritah, and Ariel were spirits, but the fact that Sara’s group were demi-humans—as the humans would call them—was kept hidden. Gouki’s group had introduced themselves as people connected to Rio’s parents, but they had refrained from explaining the details of Rio’s birth without his permission.

But that aside, they had just finished exchanging the necessary greetings with each other.

“And so, I welcome you to the Galarc Kingdom,” Francois said to Gouki and Kayoko.

“We are extremely grateful for your forgiveness over how we entered your castle uninvited.” Gouki bowed his head, expressing his respect for the foreign king through his demeanor.

They were currently in the dining hall of the mansion. Although it was comparatively minor, Rio’s mansion had been damaged in the mercenary attack. The window in the drawing room was still broken, so they were gathered in the dining hall instead. They were also to be served lunch after this.

Present in the hall were Francois, Gouki, Kayoko, as well as Charlotte, Satsuki, Miharu, Celia, Sara, and Orphia. Alma was fully healed but resting just to be safe, and Latifa was keeping her company.

“Come to think of it, your people entered the castle grounds from the skies. Ha ha, it’s fine, it doesn’t bother me,” Francois said with a hearty smile. He then turned to Gouki. “We can save the details for Haruto’s return, but I would like to confirm your intentions from here. Would it be right to consider your people as Haruto’s private army—or rather, vassals? Your relationship to him seems somewhat different to that of Sara and the other girls. I am prepared to offer you a befitting status as a reward for your contribution to repelling the insurgents, if you so desire.”

“That’s another complicated matter to address... For the time being, you can think of us as cooperators instead of vassals. Sir Haruto is rather against the notion of seeing us below him,” Gouki answered with a somewhat troubled smile.

“I see... That tends to be a troubling aspect of his personality,” Francois said, returning the smile. “But I understand. Perhaps it would be best to leave this discussion until his return after all.”

“I’m sure he’ll be back in no time at all if he can fly. He may even drop by out of the blue today,” Charlotte added.

“The spirit arts you mentioned, was it? The existence of spirits is rather hard to believe, but that was how the saint was tracked, you said.”

Francois’s words were uttered with the knowledge of Aishia’s identity as a humanoid spirit. This wasn’t something that Sara and the others had told him intentionally—the reveal of their spirits had allowed Charlotte to guess that Rio had one as well, which then led to the guess that Aishia tracked the saint by being in spirit form.

“Umm... Haruto may have returned just now,” Sara interrupted, raising her hand.

“Why, I will go meet him at the front gate immediately.” Charlotte shot to her feet in delight.

“Wouldn’t he be surprised to see you knowingly waiting for him?” Satsuki asked, pointing out how he wasn’t aware that she knew about spirits now.

“That’s what makes it interesting,” Charlotte replied with a thrilled look.

Satsuki was drawn into grinning along. “In that case, I might as well tag along.”

And so, it was decided that a group of them would go out to meet Rio.

◇ ◇ ◇

Charlotte, Satsuki, Miharu, and Celia had gone out to meet Rio at the front gate of the castle.

They watched as Rio and the others walked towards them from the noble district with Liselotte.

“He really brought her back... Amazing...” Satsuki muttered. Her tone was more hopeful and awed than exasperated. He was much more of a hero than her, she thought.

“It’s Sir Haruto, after all.” Charlotte nodded with a triumphant expression, as though it was only natural.

“It’s amazing how convincing those words can be.”

“Right?”

Satsuki and Miharu exchanged strained smiles.

“Just as we expected, he looks surprised to see us. Shall we go to him?” Celia looked at Rio’s rounded eyes from afar and giggled with a dimpled smile.

“Yes, let’s go. Hey, Haruto!” Satsuki waved her arms while breaking into a jog. Charlotte followed behind her. They eventually got close enough to speak to him.

“Welcome back, Haruto! Liselotte, Aishia, and Aria too!” Satsuki said, beaming.

“Hello... We’ve returned.” Rio was still confused.

“Hee hee. A lot happened while you were away, Sir Haruto.” Delighted by his confusion, Charlotte walked up to Rio and entangled herself around his arm. She then tugged on it once before turning to speak to Liselotte. “I’m so glad you’re safe, Liselotte. Welcome back.”

“Thank you, Princess Charlotte.”

Like Rio, Liselotte looked bewildered.

“I’ve completed your entry procedures, so please tell me everything that happened. Gouki and the others are also waiting at the mansion,” Charlotte said teasingly, peering at Rio’s face.

“...”

Rio was at a loss for words. He was clearly wondering what in the world had happened while he was gone.

“Stop that, Char. These two still haven’t given their greetings yet,” Satsuki said, scolding Charlotte for trying to monopolize Rio’s attention. “I have a lot I want to say too, but Celia and Miharu worked really hard while Haruto was gone, remember? So let them talk to him too. Go on, you two.”

She pushed the hesitant Miharu and Celia towards Rio.

“Erm...”

They exchanged slightly embarrassed looks with each other.

“Welcome back.”

They celebrated Rio’s return with gentle smiles.